Vasyl Ulianovskyi



Contacts

- Vasyl Ulianovskyi
- in Vasyl Ulianovskyi
- ≥ vasia.kit434@gmail.com
- +380730347558
- **◆ Vasyl Ulianovskyi**

Languages

Ukrainian English Polish

Summary

I started learning frontend development, 'cause I always wanted work in IT indusrty. Now I was learn HTML/CSS/JS development and search job in some IT company to the post junior frontend deleloper. I have experience in teamwork and personnel management. My personal qualities is purposeful sociable, stressful, responsible for work, punctual, without bad habits, organized.

Skills

- HTML
- Git

React

• CSS

• JavaScript

Experience

Frontend Developer at Eleks Bootcamp March 2022 - Jule 2022

HTML/CSS/JS Developer at Pluralsight January 2022 - March 2022

Education

Department of International Economic Relations 2013-2018 Lviv Polytechnic National University, Ukraine.